<?xml version="1.0"?>
<TextLibrary>

   <Text tag="[COMP_NDKH_NAME]">Syrus Darkhunter</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NDKH_DESC]">Darkhunter does 10 points of damage to any Undead creature at the start of a battle.</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NDKH_ACTV]">Undead are my specialty.  I will fill it with arrows before it even reaches you.</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NDKH_DEPT]">Farewell then, friend.  I shall be near Gallia in the Borderlands if you need my help.</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NDKH_GBYE]"></Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NDKH_RACE]">Half-Elf</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NDKH_GNDR]">Male</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NDKH_FLAV]">Syrus Darkhunter is a mysterious warrior from the Borderlands. Relatively young, he has earned a fearsome reputation as a hunter of Undead creatures. He is silent and thoughtful, and does not like to discuss his past.</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NDRO_NAME]">Drong</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NDRO_DESC]">Drong does 10 points of damage to any Animal at the start of a battle.</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NDRO_ACTV]">Yum yum yum.  Drong going to take a bite of this creature.</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NDRO_DEPT]">Bye bye! Drong wait for you in his Tower if you need him again.</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NDRO_GBYE]"></Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NDRO_RACE]">Ogre</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NDRO_GNDR]">Male</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NDRO_FLAV]">Drong is a massively fat Ogre with a remarkably friendly nature, who never seems to stop eating. It is entirely possible that there is nothing in the Realms of Etheria that Drong will not try to devour, given half a chance.</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NELI_NAME]">Elistara</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NELI_DESC]">Elistara adds +10% Water Resistance against Large opponents.</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NELI_ACTV]">Stand back! I am trained to fight large creatures. My shield will protect you.</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NELI_DEPT]">If you are certain that you do not need me for now, I will await your return in Ylarie.</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NELI_GBYE]"></Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NELI_RACE]">High Elf</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NELI_GNDR]">Female</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NELI_FLAV]">Elistara is a High Elven Dragonknight. Like all of her people she is serious and efficient - a loyal companion, but a dangerous enemy.</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NFLI_NAME]">Flicker</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NFLI_DESC]">Flicker adds +10 to your Air Resistance when fighting Fliers.</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NFLI_ACTV]">This creature can fly. I&apos;ll help keep it off of you!</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NFLI_DEPT]">I will be back in the Dragonrealm if you need me.</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NFLI_GBYE]"></Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NFLI_RACE]">Dragon</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NFLI_GNDR]">Male</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NFLI_FLAV]">Flicker is a young Gold Dragon, whose parents have gone missing, along with all the other Dragons in the Dragon Realm. Flicker is quick-witted and often rude, but has joined the party to help locate his family and friends.</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NKHA_NAME]">Khalkus</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NKHA_DESC]">Khalkus adds +10 to your Battle when fighting against Citadels or Mechanical foes.</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NKHA_ACTV]">Oh aye, I know how to fix this. I can help ye fight this one.</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NKHA_DEPT]">Farewell. If ye want me, I&apos;ll be back in the Hammer Pass waitin&apos; for ye.</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NKHA_GBYE]"></Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NKHA_RACE]">Dwarf</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NKHA_GNDR]">Male</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NKHA_FLAV]">Khalkus is a Dwarven Engineer from the mines of Khaz-Agar. He is fascinated by all things mechanical, and often talks at great length about his current projects and future plans.</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NPAT_NAME]">Patch</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NPAT_DESC]">Patch has a 20% chance to backstab an opponent for 25 points of damage.</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NPAT_ACTV]">Surprise!!! Say hello to my little friend...</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NPAT_DEPT]">You... you don&apos;t want me? If you change your mind I will wait for you in Hyaan.</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NPAT_GBYE]"></Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NPAT_RACE]">Gnoll</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NPAT_GNDR]">Male</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NPAT_FLAV]">Patch is a crazed and psychotic Gnoll Thief. Despite being a little unstable, he is fiercely loyal to those he knows and trusts, perhaps even a little overprotective of them.</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NSER_NAME]">Princess Serephine</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NSER_DESC]">Serephine adds +10 to your Battle when fighting Good opponents.</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NSER_ACTV]">Allow me to charm your opponent.  They will not strike a lady.</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NSER_DEPT]">You have been kind to me and I am willing to travel further. I will wait for you in Bartonia.</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NSER_GBYE]"></Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NSER_RACE]">Human</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NSER_GNDR]">Female</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NSER_FLAV]">Serephine is the daughter of the Selentine Emperor, whom you rescued from an arranged marriage to the Barbarian Lord, Trarg.  Serephine is beautiful and charming, and always manages to get her own way.</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NSUN_NAME]">Sunspear</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NSUN_DESC]">Sunspear adds +10 to Red Mana when fighting Minotaurs.</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NSUN_ACTV]">Fire is your greatest ally when fighting a Minotaur!</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NSUN_DEPT]">Farewell, young warrior, I shall wait for you at the Horned Temple.</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NSUN_GBYE]"></Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NSUN_RACE]">Minotaur</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NSUN_GNDR]">Male</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NSUN_FLAV]">Sunspear is an old and wise Minotaur Firewalker, assigned to you by his leader, Tauron Flamebite. Although he is not the warrior he once was, Sunspear is wise and knowledgeable in the ways of the Realms of War.</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NSUS_NAME]">Sunspear&apos;s Spirit</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NSUS_DESC]">Sunspear&apos;s Spirit adds +10 to Red Mana when fighting Undead or Minotaurs.</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NSUS_ACTV]">I have seen into the realm beyond. Let me aid you against this foe.</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NSUS_DEPT]">Farewell, young warrior, My spirit will wait for you at the Horned Temple.</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NSUS_GBYE]"></Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NSUS_RACE]">Minotaur Spirit</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NSUS_GNDR]">Male</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NSUS_FLAV]">Sunspear was an old and wise Minotaur Firewalker. He achieved great honor being slain in battle against Ragnar and his spirit has now returned to aid you.</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NWIN_NAME]">Winter</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NWIN_DESC]">Winter halves the starting mana of any opponent whose Fire Mastery is 15 or higher.</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NWIN_ACTV]">This creature is born of fire.  My icy breath will drain their mana!</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NWIN_DEPT]">I will return to my pack.  If you need me, I can be found near Tirianin.</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NWIN_GBYE]"></Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NWIN_RACE]">Wolf</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NWIN_GNDR]">Male</Text>
   <Text tag="[COMP_NWIN_FLAV]">Winter Wolves are a rare breed of Wolf found only in the Northern Tundra.  They are almost always pack leaders and masters of the hunt. Their icy breath can slow an enemy in its tracks.</Text>

</TextLibrary>
