<?xml version="1.0"?>
<TextLibrary>

   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MARB_NAME]">Arboleth</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MARB_DESC]">Arboleths are violent and mindless creatures of chaos. They absorb energy from enemy spells to heal themselves.  They can also use the Consume Mana spell to power the Chaos Bolt spell.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MARB_CAPT]">You have captured an Arboleth. Once you have built a Mage Tower in your capital city, you will be able to learn the Consume Mana and Chaos Bolt spells from this creature.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MARK_NAME]">Arkliche</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MARK_DESC]">Arkliches, like Liches, have abilities and items to create Skulls. They also have high Fire Resistance and can use the Soul Swap spell to swap mana with their opponent.  In addition, Arkliches have items that can reduce your Experience Points.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MARK_CAPT]">You have captured an Arkliche.  Once you have built a Mage Tower in your capital city, you will be able to learn the Soul Swap spell from this creature.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MBAN_NAME]">Lord Bane (Boss)</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MBAN_DESC]">Lord Bane is immensely powerful. He has spells which can destroy Mana Gems and improve his skills, while his items increase his power based on those skills.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MBAN_CAPT]"></Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MBAT_NAME]">Giant Bat</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MBAT_DESC]">Giant Bats are able to Swoop, draining you of half your Yellow Mana.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MBAT_CAPT]">You have captured a Giant Bat.  Once you have built a Mage Tower in your capital city, you will be able to learn the Swoop spell from this creature.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MCEN_NAME]">Centaur</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MCEN_DESC]">Not only can the Centaur Trample you (doing half his Green Mana in damage), but he also has a special Archery skill that allows him to do damage equal to YOUR Yellow Mana, so don&apos;t save up too much!</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MCEN_CAPT]">You have captured a Centaur.  Once you have built a Mage Tower in your capital city, you will be able to learn the Trample and Archery spells from this creature.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MCIT_NAME]">Citadel</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MCIT_DESC]">A Citadel must be fought like a regular monster, but if you are victorious, you then add it to your Kingdom.  Citadels are very powerful and take some time to beat.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MCIT_CAPT]">N/A</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MCTP_NAME]">Catapult</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MCTP_DESC]">The Catapult has the Besiege skill, which allows it to lob exploding missiles into random places on the grid.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MCTP_CAPT]">You have captured a Catapult.  Once you have built a Mage Tower in your capital city, you will be able to learn the Besiege skill from it.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MDDW_NAME]">Dark Dwarf</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MDDW_DESC]">Dark Dwarves are extremely cunning. Not only can they duplicate your items, but they can also attach Firebombs to your character that explode if your Red Mana is too high.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MDDW_CAPT]">You have captured a Dark Dwarf.  Once you have built a Mage Tower in your capital city, you will be able to learn the Firebomb and Flamecannon spells from this creature.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MDGG_NAME]">Dugog (Boss)</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MDGG_DESC]">As well as having the skills of a regular Ogre, Dugog&apos;s Extra Head gives him another turn when he collects Gold. His club is very dangerous and randomly does huge amounts of damage.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MDGG_CAPT]">-</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MDOO_NAME]">Doomknight</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MDOO_DESC]">Doomknights are able to create Green Gems with the Burial spell and then use their Green Mana to damage their opponents.  They can also use all of their Green Mana to attack enemies with the Sword of Bane spell.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MDOO_CAPT]">You have captured a Doomknight.  Once you have built a Mage Tower in your capital city, you will be able to learn the Sword of Bane and Burial spells from this creature.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MDRB_NAME]">Frost Dragon</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MDRB_DESC]">Frost Dragons can deal massive amounts of damage. They Breathe Ice, which does damage equal to their Blue Mana. They can also stun enemies with their Wing Buffet.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MDRB_CAPT]">You have captured a Frost Dragon. Once you have built a Mage Tower in your capital city, you will be able to learn the Channel Water spell from this creature.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MDRG_NAME]">Swamp Dragon</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MDRG_DESC]">Swamp Dragons can deal massive amounts of damage. They Breathe Poison, which does damage equal to their Green Mana and causes Poison. They can also stun enemies with their Wing Buffet.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MDRG_CAPT]">You have captured a Swamp Dragon. Once you have built a Mage Tower in your capital city, you will be able to learn the Channel Earth spell from this creature.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MDRR_NAME]">Flame Dragon</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MDRR_DESC]">Flame Dragons can deal massive amounts of damage. They Breathe Fire, which does damage equal to their Red Mana. They can also stun enemies with their Wing Buffet.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MDRR_CAPT]">You have captured a Flame Dragon. Once you have built a Mage Tower in your capital city, you will be able to learn the Channel Fire spell from this creature.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MDRU_NAME]">Undead Dragon</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MDRU_DESC]">Undead Dragons can deal massive amounts of damage. They Breathe Plague, which does damage equal to their Yellow Mana and causes Disease. They can also stun enemies with their Wing Buffet.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MDRU_CAPT]">You have captured an Undead Dragon. Once you have built a Mage Tower in your capital city, you will be able to learn the Channel Air spell from this creature.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MDSP_NAME]">Dragon Spider</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MDSP_DESC]">As well as inflicting Poison, which can slowly drain Life Points, Dragon Spiders are also able to Web their opponents and to Breathe Fire on them.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MDSP_CAPT]">The Dragon Spider is a slow mount. It gives you the Breathe Fire spell and increases your Fire Mastery by +2 (+1 more per 2 levels).</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MELG_NAME]">Elven Guard</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MELG_DESC]">Elven Guards become dangerous, doing extra damage, if their Green Mana becomes high. They can also cast various nature spells including Entangle and Gemberry.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MELG_CAPT]">You have captured an Eleven Guard.  Once you have built a Mage Tower in your capital city, you will be able to learn the Entangle and Gemberry spells from him.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MFEL_NAME]">Fire Elemental</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MFEL_DESC]">Not only can the Fire Elemental use Wall of Fire to shield itself from damage, but it can also drain your Red Mana and use it for healing.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MFEL_CAPT]">You have captured a Fire Elemental.  Once you have built a Mage Tower in your capital city, you will be able to learn the Fire Siphon and Wall of Fire spells from him.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MFGI_NAME]">Frost Giant</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MFGI_DESC]">Frost Giants are able to use their special skills to increase the number of Blue Gems in play.  Also, their damage increases with the number of Blue Gems, so be wary of letting too many appear!</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MFGI_CAPT]">You have captured a Frost Giant.  Once you have built a Mage Tower in your capital city, you will be able to learn the Freeze and Frostbite spells from him.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MGNL_NAME]">Gnoll</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MGNL_DESC]">A single Gnoll is quite weak, but as a combat progresses he will get tougher and tougher gradually calling his pack each time he gains Experience or Gold.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MGNL_CAPT]">You have captured a Gnoll.  Once you have built a Mage Tower in your capital city, you will be able to learn the Sense Blood spell from this creature.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MGOB_NAME]">Goblin</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MGOB_DESC]">Goblins are able to Hide in the midst of combat. A hidden opponent does double damage when they hit you. The Goblin remains hidden until you damage him.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MGOB_CAPT]">You have captured a Goblin.  Once you have built a Mage Tower in your capital city, you will be able to learn the Hide spell from this creature.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MGRI_NAME]">Griffon</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MGRI_DESC]">Not only can Griffons convert all Green and Blue Gems to Yellow, but they can also use their Death Dive skill to inflict damage equal to the number of Yellow Gems in play.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MGRI_CAPT]">The Griffon is a fast flying mount. It gives you the Death Dive spell and increases your Air Mastery by +2 (+1 more per 2 levels).</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MGSH_NAME]">Gobshooter</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MGSH_DESC]">The Gobshooter not only Besieges like a regular Catapult, but it also Hurls Goblins at its foes.  A Goblin hits a random gem, destroys it, and then gives an additional 20 times its effect.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MGSH_CAPT]">You have captured a Gobshooter.  Once you have built a Mage Tower in your capital city, you will be able to learn the Hurl Goblin skill from it.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MGSP_NAME]">Giant Spider</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MGSP_DESC]">As well as inflicting Poison, which can slowly drain Life Points, Giant Spiders are also able to use a Web that can trap their opponents for a number of turns.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MGSP_CAPT]">The Giant Spider is a slow mount. It gives you the Web spell and increases your Battle skill by +1 (+1 more per 3 levels).</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MGUU_NAME]">Gruulkar (Boss)</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MGUU_DESC]">As well as having the skills of a regular Orc Lord, Gruulkar has a shield that increases his Battle skill every time he is hit.  Not only that, but his Great Axe gives him extra turns when doing damage.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MGUU_CAPT]">-</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MGWA_NAME]">Giant Wasp</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MGWA_DESC]">Giant Wasps are very dangerous. Their Deathsting attack Poisons and does massive damage, while they can also summon a Swarm to increase their Morale and Life Points.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MGWA_CAPT]">You have captured a Giant Wasp.  Once you have built a Mage Tower in your capital city, you will be able to learn the Swarm spell from him.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MHAR_NAME]">Harpy</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MHAR_DESC]">Not only can Harpies swoop, draining half your Yellow Mana, but they can also use the Charm spell, which destroys all Skulls in play, and gives them a point of Healing for each one destroyed.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MHAR_CAPT]">You have captured a Harpy.  Once you have built a Mage Tower in your capital city, you will be able to learn the Charm spell from this creature.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MHGI_NAME]">Hill Giant</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MHGI_DESC]">Hill Giants can Thump! you doing a straight 10 points of damage, or they can Stomp! which destroys all Green Gems and causes you to miss a turn.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MHGI_CAPT]">You have captured a Hill Giant.  Once you have built a Mage Tower in your capital city, you will be able to learn the Thump! and Stomp! spells from this creature.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MIGO_NAME]">Iron Golem</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MIGO_DESC]">The Iron Skin and Iron Fists of these Golems make them very difficult to damage and very tough to fight.  Their Iron Strike spell uses massive amounts of Green Mana to explode all Green Gems.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MIGO_CAPT]">You have captured an Iron Golem.  Once you have built a Mage Tower in your capital city, you will be able to learn the Iron Strike spell from this creature.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MIMG_NAME]">Imperial Guard</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MIMG_DESC]">Imperial Guards may call for Reinforcements, using Gold Coins to heal themselves in combat.  They may also Thrust at a single Gem to destroy it.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MIMG_CAPT]">You have captured an Imperial Guard.  Once you have built a Mage Tower in your capital city, you will be able to learn the Reinforcements spell from him.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MIMP_NAME]">Imp</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MIMP_DESC]">The Imp has a number of annoying spells that include the abilities to turn gems to red, drain your Mana and even do direct damage.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MIMP_CAPT]">You have captured an Imp.  Once you have built a Mage Tower in your capital city, you will be able to learn the Burn, Taunt and Zap spells from this creature.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MKNI_NAME]">Knight</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MKNI_DESC]">Knights may Thrust at a single chosen grid on the board, destroying a gem.  They may also call upon the power of Divine Right to destroy all Purple Stars in play.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MKNI_CAPT]">You have captured a Knight.  Once you have built a Mage Tower in your capital city, you will be able to learn the Thrust and Divine Right spells from him.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MLIA_NAME]">Liandra (Boss)</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MLIA_DESC]">Liandra, like an Arkliche, has the Death Gaze and Soul Swap spells along with a high Fire Resistance. She also has the ability to cast Charm (for healing herself) and Chaos Bolt (for direct damage).</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MLIA_CAPT]"></Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MLIC_NAME]">Liche</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MLIC_DESC]">Liches - with both their items and spells - are prone to create Skulls all over the grid.  They can also use their Green Mana to cast Death Gaze, which halves your Life Points.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MLIC_CAPT]">You have captured a Liche.  Once you have built a Mage Tower in your citadel, you will be able to learn the Death Gaze and Wake the Dead spells from this creature.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MMCH_NAME]">Mechataur (Boss)</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MMCH_DESC]">As well as having the skills of a regular Minotaur, the Mechataur can Energize, healing large amounts of damage, and can also use its Mechanical Axe to get extra turns when dealing damage.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MMCH_CAPT]">-</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MMED_NAME]">Medusa</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MMED_DESC]">As well as inflicting Poison and turning Green Gems into Skulls, a Medusa is able to use her Green Mana to Paralyze you, causing you to miss 2 turns.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MMED_CAPT]">You have captured a Medusa.  Once you have built a Mage Tower in your capital city, you will be able to learn the Stone Gaze and Petrify spells from this creature.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MMGO_NAME]">Minogoth (Boss)</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MMGO_DESC]">Minogoth is a Minotaur Doomknight. As well as being able to Charge like a bull and manipulate Skulls like an Undead creature, he also destroys all Purple Stars whenever matching 4 or 5 of a kind.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MMGO_CAPT]"></Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MMIK_NAME]">Minotaur King</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MMIK_DESC]">As well as the simple ability to deal huge amounts of damage, Minotaur Kings are able to use the Berserk Rage spell to turn Red Gems into Skulls.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MMIK_CAPT]">You have captured a Minotaur King.  Once you have built a Mage Tower in your capital city, you will be able to learn the Berserk Rage spell from this creature.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MMIN_NAME]">Minotaur</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MMIN_DESC]">Minotaurs not only have a Great Axe which increases their damage and gives them extra turns, but they can also Charge, destroying a whole row of gems.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MMIN_CAPT]">You have captured a Minotaur.  Once you have built a Mage Tower in your capital city, you will be able to learn the Charge! spell from this creature.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MNEC_NAME]">Necromancer</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MNEC_DESC]">Necromancers are difficult to fight because they are experts at draining your Mana Reserves. They also can use the Bone Avatar spell to increase their Battle skill.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MNEC_CAPT]">You have captured a Necromancer.  Once you have built a Mage Tower in your capital city, you will be able to learn the Dark Bolt and Bone Avatar spells from this creature.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MOGM_NAME]">Ogre Mage</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MOGM_DESC]">As well as dealing out large amounts of damage, Ogre Mages are able to randomly create Wildcards amongst the gems. Their items also help to generate Mana and create +5 Skulls.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MOGM_CAPT]">You have captured an Ogre Mage.  Once you have built a Mage Tower in your capital city, you will be able to learn the Thump! and Wild Magic spells from this creature.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MOGR_NAME]">Ogre</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MOGR_DESC]">Ogres use their Spiked Clubs to generate Red Mana.  They then use that Red Mana to cast Thump! and damage their opponents.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MOGR_CAPT]">You have captured an Ogre.  Once you have built a Mage Tower in your capital city, you will be able to learn the Thump! spell from this creature.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MOLO_NAME]">Orc Lord</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MOLO_DESC]">Orc Lords can not only become Enraged like regular Orcs, but they can also Stun their opponents with a Headbutt and Call the Horde, increasing their Mana and Life Points.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MOLO_CAPT]">You have captured an Orc Lord.  Once you have built a Mage Tower in your capital city, you will be able to learn the Headbutt and Call the Horde spells from this creature.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MORC_NAME]">Orc</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MORC_DESC]">Orcs can use their Red Mana to become Enraged. An Enraged opponent has his Battle skill increased and does more damage.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MORC_CAPT]">You have captured an Orc.  Once you have built a Mage Tower in your capital city, you will be able to learn the Enrage spell from this creature.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MRAT_NAME]">Giant Rat</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MRAT_DESC]">Not only can Rats Scavenge all the Gold in play, but they can also inflict Disease. Disease is a status effect that lasts a number of turns and automatically lowers your Mana every turn.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MRAT_CAPT]">The Giant Rat is a slow mount. It gives you the Rabid Bite spell and increases your Cunning skill by +1 (+1 more per 4 levels).</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MRAX_NAME]">Red-Axe (Boss)</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MRAX_DESC]">As well as having the skills of a regular Minotaur, Red-Axe has a powerful magical axe and a spell that allows him to throw it.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MRAX_CAPT]">-</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MSCO_NAME]">Scorpion</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MSCO_DESC]">Not only can Scorpions Poison you, but they are also able to Hide.  Hidden creatures do double damage and remain hidden until they themselves take some damage.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MSCO_CAPT]">The Scorpion is a slow mount. It gives you the Hide spell and increases your Earth Mastery by +1 (+1 more per 3 levels).</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MSKE_NAME]">Skeleton</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MSKE_DESC]">Not only can Skeletons drain your Mana with their Chill Touch spell, but they can also Wake the Dead, turning ordinary Skulls into +5 Skulls.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MSKE_CAPT]">You have captured a Skeleton. Once you have built a Mage Tower in your capital city, you will be able to learn the Chill Touch and Wake the Dead spells from this creature.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MSKT_NAME]">Skelotaur</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MSKT_DESC]">Skelotaurs can charge like a Minotaur and drain Mana and create Red Skulls like a Skeleton.  They can also drain your Green Mana with the Bone Strike spell.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MSKT_CAPT]">You have captured a Skelotaur.  Once you have built a Mage Tower in your capital city, you will be able to learn the Bone Strike spell from this creature.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MSSP_NAME]">Sea Serpent</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MSSP_DESC]">Sea Serpents are able to Submerge, doubling their Blue Mana.  They can use this Mana to Spit Poison which both Blinds and Poisons their enemies (leaving the enemy unable to cast spells and slowly losing Life Points).</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MSSP_CAPT]">You have captured a Sea Serpent.  Once you have built a Mage Tower in your capital city, you will be able to learn the Spit Poison and Submerge spells from this creature.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MSWO_NAME]">Sandworm</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MSWO_DESC]">Not only can Sandworms Hide (doing double damage while hidden), but they also have a nasty combination of skills.  They use Sinkhole to increase your Green Mana, then Swallow Whole which damages you based on your Green Mana!</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MSWO_CAPT]">The Sandworm is slow mount. It gives you the Swallow Whole spell and increases your Earth Mastery by +2 (+1 more per 2 levels).</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MTHF_NAME]">Thief</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MTHF_DESC]">Not only can Thieves perform a Sneak Attack, doing small amounts of damage and not ending their turn, but they can also Steal your hard-earned Gold.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MTHF_CAPT]">You have captured a Thief.  Once you have built a Mage Tower in your capital city, you will be able to learn the Sneak Attack and Steal spells from him.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MTRO_NAME]">Troll</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MTRO_DESC]">Trolls can use their Blue Mana to regenerate Life Points.  As long as it has enough Mana, a Troll may Regenerate as many times in its turn as it wishes.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MTRO_CAPT]">You have captured a Troll.  Once you have built a Mage Tower in your capital city, you will be able to learn the Regenerate spell from this creature.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MTUT_NAME]">Practice Dummy</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MTUT_DESC]">The Practice Dummy is the easiest of opponents to fight, since it puts up no resistance.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MTUT_CAPT]">There is little point capturing a practice dummy, since it cannot teach you any spells.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MVBT_NAME]">Vampire Bat</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MVBT_DESC]">Vampire Bats can not only Swoop upon you, draining half your Yellow Mana, but they can also drain your Life Points and add up to 5 points to their own Life total.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MVBT_CAPT]">You have captured a Vampire Bat.  Once you have built a Mage Tower in your capital city, you will be able to learn the Vampirism spell from this creature.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MVGI_NAME]">Fire Giant</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MVGI_DESC]">Fire Giants are able to use Conflagration to increase the number of Red Gems in play.  They can then use their Flameblade and Rain of Fire spells to have these gems increase damage!</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MVGI_CAPT]">You have captured a Fire Giant.  Once you have built a Mage Tower in your capital city, you will be able to learn the Rain of Fire and Conflagration spells from him.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MWIG_NAME]">Wight</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MWIG_DESC]">Wights can drain Mana with their spells and their evil Wightblades. They can use some of this drained Mana to cast Spectral Force, which freezes enemies in place.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MWIG_CAPT]">You have captured a Wight. Once you have built a Mage Tower in your capital city, you will be able to learn the Chill Touch and Spectral Force spells from this creature.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MWLF_NAME]">Wolf</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MWLF_DESC]">Wolves can inflict Disease with their Rabid Bite (slowly draining your Mana). They can also Howl, which inflicts Fear for 5 turns (halving all your skills).</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MWLF_CAPT]">The Wolf is a fast mount. It gives you the Howl spell and increases your Water Mastery by +1 (+1 more per 3 levels).</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MWRI_NAME]">Wolfrider</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MWRI_DESC]">Wolfriders combine the skills of Orcs and Wolves. They Howl to inflict Fear (halving skills), Bite to inflict Disease, and can also become Enraged, increasing their Battle skill.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MWRI_CAPT]">You have captured a Wolfrider.  Once you have built a Mage Tower in your capital city, you will be able to learn the Enrage spell from this creature.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MWYV_NAME]">Wyvern</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MWYV_DESC]">Wyverns inflict a particularly nasty Poison, draining your Life Points.  They can also use the Rend spell, which inflicts damage without ending their turn.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MWYV_CAPT]">The Wyvern is a flying mount of average speed. It gives you the Rend spell and increases your Battle skill by +2 (+1 more per 2 levels).</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MZOM_NAME]">Zombie</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MZOM_DESC]">Zombies can inflict Disease, which will drain your Mana every turn.  They may also Eat Skulls, gaining +1 to their Battle skill for each Skull devoured.</Text>
   <Text tag="[MONSTER_MZOM_CAPT]">You have captured a Zombie. Once you have built a Mage Tower in your capital city, you will be able to learn the Eat Skulls spell from this creature.</Text>

</TextLibrary>
