<?xml version="1.0"?>
<TextLibrary>

   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U000_NAME]">Knightly Orders</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U000_DESC]">There are five Orders of Knights in Agaria - the Bartonians are the largest, but each of the other four Orders--Sirians, Elenians, Theirans and Gildines--is equally prestigious in their own way.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U001_NAME]">Darkhunter&apos;s History</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U001_DESC]">It is rumored that Syrus Darkhunter was once a Riverguard Knight, but was exiled from the Order after an argument with its leader, Lord Greythane.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U002_NAME]">Drakenburg&apos;s Dragon</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U002_DESC]">The Green Dragon who lives in the mountains north of Drakenburg has not been seen for some time.  The folk of Drakenburg are not sorry to see him go!</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U003_NAME]">Griffons</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U003_DESC]">The Dwarves up in the Agarian Pass have reported seeing many Griffons, Ogres and Orcs recently. The pass is a dangerous place and they recommend keeping travel there to a minimum.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U004_NAME]">Imperial Wedding</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U004_DESC]">The people of The Trarg are very excited about the upcoming wedding of their leader to the Imperial Princess, Serephine.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U005_NAME]">Bartonia</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U005_DESC]">Bartonia is the largest of the citadels in the Agarian Empire. Many young nobles and squires are sent here to train as part of their education.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U006_NAME]">Palace Guard</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U006_DESC]">The Palace Guard of Bartonia is a popular training academy for young nobles. There, they can learn basic magic, fighting skills and how to behave in the royal court.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U007_NAME]">Mounts</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U007_DESC]">The people of the Trarg tell you that a mount moves you faster, and that a well-trained mount can help you avoid many encounters. To get a mount you should first build a Dungeon in your citadel.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U008_NAME]">The Borderlands</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U008_DESC]">Once part of the mighty Lysean Empire before its fall, the Borderlands is now a region of small Duchies ruled over by numerous petty Barons and Dukes.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U009_NAME]">Riverguard</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U009_DESC]">The Knights of the Riverguard live in the Red Tower, inside the Citadel of Maethelburg. They patrol the river to help keep their part of the Borderlands safe.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U010_NAME]">Wood Elves</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U010_DESC]">Wood Elves are the least populous of the three Elven peoples (High Elves, Dark Elves and Wood Elves). They only have two settlements in Etheria--Silvermyr and Solhaven, which is on the Isle of Dawn.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U011_NAME]">Wood Elf Royalty</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U011_DESC]">The Wood Elves of Silvermyr are ruled by King Oberon and Queen Titania. They have been close allies of the Agarian Knights for many centuries.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U012_NAME]">Skellheim</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U012_DESC]">The evil decrepit Duke of Skellheim rules this swampy land in the middle of the Borderlands. Many folks say that he is a Necromancer.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U013_NAME]">Dhun-Kor</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U013_DESC]">The Dwarven outpost of Dhun-Kor was established to trade with the Orcs and Goblins on the plains of Kor. Typically Dwarves hate Orcs, but if there is a profit involved they can put hatred aside.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U014_NAME]">The Great Orc</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U014_DESC]">This position - leader of the Orc tribes of Kor - is chosen by combat. The title is in many ways irrelevant since it has been many centuries since a Great Orc united enough tribes to cross the mountains and do any serious damage.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U015_NAME]">Gruuldok</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U015_DESC]">Not too long ago, Gruuldok was only a small Orcish tribal village.  It has risen to prominence since its chieftain Gruulkar became the Great Orc.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U016_NAME]">Ogre Cooking</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U016_DESC]">Ogres are amongst the worst cooks in Etheria.  There is nothing an Ogre will not throw in his pot to make a meal. Some Sages believe that Ogres actually have no tastebuds at all.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U017_NAME]">Ogre Mages</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U017_DESC]">The Ogres are ruled by a council of Ogre Mages. These creatures are feared by many because they control a wild chaotic form of magic. Sadly, the only thing more chaotic than their magic is their form of government.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U018_NAME]">Dragons</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U018_DESC]">Many types of Dragons usually inhabit the Dragonrealm, each of them a different color. There are Flame Dragons, Frost Dragons, Swamp Dragons, and Storm Dragons.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U019_NAME]">Kelthurax</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U019_DESC]">Kelthurax, the ancient Flame Dragon, is perhaps the oldest creature still alive in Etheria today. He can still remember the Sundering almost 3000 years ago, when half the world was destroyed.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U020_NAME]">Firewalkers</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U020_DESC]">Firewalkers are Minotaur Priests, worshippers of Lord Sartek.  Since Sartek fell in battle, their power in the Realms of War has been waning.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U021_NAME]">Sartek&apos;s Treachery</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U021_DESC]">Lord Bane attacked his brother Lord Sartek because Lord Bane was angry when Sartek withdrew from battle against the Agarian Knights in the Banewars, 500 years ago.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U022_NAME]">The Four Horsemen</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U022_DESC]">Lord Sartek and Lord Bane are two of the Four Horsemen -- War and Death. Lords Antharg and Melchor -- Plague and Famine -- live far away in the south and west.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U023_NAME]">Gnolls</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U023_DESC]">Gnolls were another creature created by Lord Sartek.  He grafted a dog&apos;s head onto a Human body.  Gnolls are cunning and fast, and they attack in packs.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U024_NAME]">Trouble in Hyaan</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U024_DESC]">Just like most canine creatures, the Gnolls of Hyaan are constantly struggling for dominance.  Currently a Gnoll called Staf is trying to take over their city.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U025_NAME]">Ohtar</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U025_DESC]">The huge Palace of Ohtar was home to Lord Sartek for many, many centuries before Lord Bane exacted his revenge.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U026_NAME]">Ylarie Ruins</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U026_DESC]">Ylarie was overrun many centuries ago by an Orc named Gornak Elfeater. Strangely, the High Elves never rebuilt the city.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U027_NAME]">High Elven Royalty</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U027_DESC]">The High Elves are ruled by two monarchs, the Ice Queen who lives in Ehlariel, and the Moon King who lives on the isle of Lunarion.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U028_NAME]">The Passes of Death</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U028_DESC]">Three passes exist into the Realms of Death, two of which are guarded by the High Elves.  They are called Skullguard Pass and Iceguard Pass.  The two Keeps in these passes have not fallen since the Banewars, 500 years ago.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U029_NAME]">Ragnar the Dragon</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U029_DESC]">Ragnar is an ancient Frost Dragon who can often be found on the coast to the west of Ehlariel.  He has lived in the nearby mountains so long that they are now known as the Mountains of Ragnar.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U030_NAME]">The Banewars</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U030_DESC]">Five hundred years ago, Lord Bane staged a massive invasion throughout Etheria but was finally pushed back by the Sirian Knights who defeated him.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U031_NAME]">Bane&apos;s Revenge</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U031_DESC]">One hundred years after he fell in the Banewars, Lord Bane rose again.  This time he made a surgically precise strike into Agaria to slay the knights who defeated him in battle.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U032_NAME]">Lord Bane&apos;s Citadel</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U032_DESC]">This Citadel of Lord Bane is a mass of interconnecting torture chambers and dungeons, filled with the screams of victims. Bane works tirelessly to create new Undead creatures.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U033_NAME]">Dark Dwarves</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U033_DESC]">Dark Dwarves were once members of the regular Dwarven Clans. After the Great Dwarven Plague, they set out on a long journey. Unfortunately Bane corrupted them as they passed through his lands.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U034_NAME]">Great Dwarven Plague</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U034_DESC]">When the Dwarves of Khaz-Barak tunneled too near the Realms of Plague, Lord Antharg inflicted them with a terrible disease that killed nearly a third of them.  They have never fully recovered from this.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U035_NAME]">Sir Ector</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U035_DESC]">Sir Ector was once a Knight of Siria. When his lands were flooded by rain and his family killed by Orcs, he grew depressed. He eventually turned to worship Lord Bane in exchange for many secrets the Dark Lord could teach him.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U036_NAME]">Selentine Empire</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U036_DESC]">Although currently at peace for over a decade, the Selentine Empire has often tried to invade Agaria, but it has always been turned back by the Elenian Knights.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U037_NAME]">The Trarg</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U037_DESC]">The Trarg is an area south of the Selentine Empire, ruled by tribes of nomadic horsemen.  They often raid the southern reaches of the Empire.  Because they are nomads, they have proven difficult to conquer.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U038_NAME]">Conflict with Bane</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U038_DESC]">Lord Bane and the Agarian Knights have a rivalry extending back many centuries. Every time the Dark Lord has tried to march south, it has been the Agarian Knights (the Sirians in particular) who have held him back and defeated him.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U039_NAME]">Sirian Allfather</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U039_DESC]">Sirian Allfather is the God worshipped by most Agarians.  He is the patron deity of justice, honor and chivalry, protector of the weak, and slayer of evil.  His church is strongest in Siria and Bartonia.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U040_NAME]">House Albion</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U040_DESC]">House Albion of Siria is one of the oldest noble houses of Agaria.  It&apos;s forefathers include the revered King Albion who almost singlehandedly defeated Lord Bane during the Banewars 500 years ago.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U041_NAME]">Queen Gwendholyn</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U041_DESC]">Queen Gwendholyn has ruled over Bartonia for fifteen years.  She has been a wise, kind and noble ruler, and during her reign Bartonia has known unequalled prosperity.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U042_NAME]">Emperor Selentius</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U042_DESC]">The people of the Selentine Empire believe their leader is a cruel, untrustworthy and manipulative man, who exploits all those he deals with.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U043_NAME]">Khrona</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U043_DESC]">Khrona is leader of the Dwarven Merchant&apos;s Guild in Dhun-Kor.  She is remarkably well-spoken for a Dwarf, having grown up and been educated in the Selentine Empire, the Borderlands, and Agaria.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U044_NAME]">Gruulkar</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U044_DESC]">Gruulkar, the current Great Orc, came to power five years ago when he lopped off the previous Great Orc&apos;s head in a ritual challenge.  Since then he has been busy trying to organize the local tribes into an effective army.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U045_NAME]">Lord Sartek</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U045_DESC]">Lord Sartek was the God of War.  He ruled undisputed over the Realms of War until 500 years ago when he was defeated by his brother Lord Bane, the God of Death.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U046_NAME]">Minotaurs</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_U046_DESC]">The Minotaurs were the greatest creation of the God Sartek.  He called them his favorite children. Their huge size and strength allowed them to capture and control most of the Realms of War.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_US00_NAME]">Undead Trouble</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_US00_DESC]">Creatures from beyond the grave -- Skeletons and Zombies -- have recently been appearing throughout Agaria.  It is all the Knights can do to hold them all back.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_US01_NAME]">Orc Slavers</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_US01_DESC]">Orc Slavers have been coming over the mountains from Kor, capturing people and hauling them away. This is unusual behavior for Orcs.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_US02_NAME]">Unrest in Kor</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_US02_DESC]">The Dwarves of Dhun-Kor are concerned that too many Orcs are joining forces with Gruulkar.  If their numbers become too great, there may well be an invasion.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_US03_NAME]">Missing Dragons</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_US03_DESC]">The Dragons of the Dragonrealm seem to have been taken away. It is believed that the Minotaurs are using some sort of machinery to capture them.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_US04_NAME]">Lord Sartek</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_US04_DESC]">Lord Sartek, the Dark Horseman of War, was the God of the Minotaurs before Lord Bane carved him up into 101 pieces and distributed him throughout Etheria.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_US05_NAME]">Minogoth</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_US05_DESC]">Lord Bane sent a Minotaur Doomknight -- a huge armored Undead Minotaur -- to occupy the city of Ohtar and bend the Minotaurs to his will.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_US06_NAME]">Lord Bane</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_US06_DESC]">Lord Bane, the Dark Horseman of Death, has ruled the Realms of Death for almost two millenia.  He commands legions of Undead creatures and has a particular hatred of the Agarian Knights.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_US07_NAME]">Dark Dwarf Trading</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUMOR_US07_DESC]">It seems that Lord Bane has been trading with the Dark Dwarves of Kal-Ungar.  Lord Bane has been paying them with metal from his conquests, and the Dwarves have been working for him.</Text>

</TextLibrary>
