<?xml version="1.0"?>
<TextLibrary>

   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q0E0_NAME]">Stolen Catapult</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q0E0_DESC]">Necromancers in Skelheim have stolen Catapults and threaten to attack Drakenburg. You must destroy the Catapults.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q0E1_NAME]">Storms At Sea</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q0E1_DESC]">Storms have been driving Sea Serpents into the Drakenburg sewers. You must clear them out.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q0I0_NAME]">Troll Trouble</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q0I0_DESC]">An old Troll, Egor the Aged, has been blocking a bridge on the River Maethel, causing trouble for all who pass by. You must chase him away.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q0I1_NAME]">Spider Bait</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q0I1_DESC]">Giant Spiders have infested the Ancient Grove where the Elenian Druids hold their ceremonies. If you can slay the largest of these spiders, the rest will probably leave.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q0I2_NAME]">Imperial Message</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q0I2_DESC]">The Queen of Bartonia needs a message delivered to the Emperor of Selentia, far away in the Selentine capital of Enmouth.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q0I3_NAME]">Slavers</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q0I3_DESC]">Some Minotaur Slavers have been harrassing the Selentine Empire. You must help drive them off.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q0I4_NAME]">The Marriage</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q0I4_DESC]">You must escort the Emperor&apos;s daughter, Princess Serephine, to the Trarg where she is to wed the leader of the Horse Tribes, Utrarg of Trarg.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q0I5_NAME]">Imperial Reply</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q0I5_DESC]">You must take the Emperor&apos;s reply back to Queen Gwendholyn in Bartonia.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q0I6_NAME]">Knightly Orders</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q0I6_DESC]">You must seek out and train with each of the 5 Orders of Agarian Knights and then choose an Order to join.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q0I7_NAME]">Bats in the Belfry</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q0I7_DESC]">Bats have infested a tower in the Royal Crypt. You must travel there and chase them away.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q0Q0_NAME]">The Missive</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q0Q0_DESC]">A sealed message must be delivered to Sir Albion in Siria.  This is an important message, and you may be in danger as you travel there.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q0Q1_NAME]">Rogue Skeleton</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q0Q1_DESC]">A Skeleton has been terrorizing the peasants near the Royal Crypt in western Theira.  Nobody is sure where it came from, though whispers say that a cult of necromancers are to blame.  You must find the Skeleton and lay it to rest.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q0Q2_NAME]">Darkhunter</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q0Q2_DESC]">Undead are beginning to appear all over Agaria.  You must travel south over the mountains in search of a warrior named Darkhunter - a specialist in combat against the Undead.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q0Q3_NAME]">Helping Hand</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q0Q3_DESC]">Darkhunter is heading out to the Skell Marshes to track down an evil Sorcerer.  He requires some help to hold the Sorcerer&apos;s minions at bay.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q0Q4_NAME]">The Prisoner</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q0Q4_DESC]">You must escort a captive Sorcerer to the Red Tower - the home citadel of the Riverguard, located in Maethelburg.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q0Q5_NAME]">Rescue Mission</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q0Q5_DESC]">A band of Orcs recently traveled over the Hammer Pass, took some prisoners and headed back to Kor.  You must try to catch them and rescue the prisoners.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q0Q6_NAME]">None Shall Pass</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q0Q6_DESC]">A strange Undead creature - a Liche - is blocking access to the forest of Silvermyr.  The Wood Elves need help fighting it.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q0Q7_NAME]">Dwarven Caravan</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q0Q7_DESC]">A Dwarf by the name of Khalkus has requested your aid in getting a caravan of supplies safely through Agaria.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q0Q8_NAME]">Good Tidings</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q0Q8_DESC]">You must deliver news of Dugog&apos;s demise to Queen Gwendholyn in Bartonia.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q0R0_NAME]">Patrol Duty</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q0R0_DESC]">The Elenian Knights regularly patrol the forests of Agaria, looking for signs of trouble.  You must perform one such patrol, traveling from Bartonia to Elenia and back again.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q0R1_NAME]">Harpy Infestation</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q0R1_DESC]">Harpies have infested the Old Outpost again - an ancient Selentine Tower on the edge of the forest that was overrun by Elenian archers 100 years ago. You must clean out the Tower.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q0S0_NAME]">Beneath Gildor</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q0S0_DESC]">Giant Rats have been plaguing Gildor. You must seek out the largest of these rats and slay it.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q0S1_NAME]">Ogre Twins</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q0S1_DESC]">A pair of Ogres have built a tower to the east.  You must go and chase them back over the mountains into Kor.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q0S2_NAME]">Dragonsearch</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q0S2_DESC]">The Green Dragon who lives in the mountains nearby has not been seen for some time. You must travel to his cave and see if he is there.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q0S3_NAME]">Father and Son</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q0S3_DESC]">A young Squire named Erik is seeking your help.  His father, Lord Michael, was captured by Orcs as they traveled past the Ogre&apos;s Tower.  You must travel there and rescue him.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q0S4_NAME]">Lord of the Swamp</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q0S4_DESC]">Every year the Elves of Silvermyr deliver a gift to Embraxus, the Dragon of the Alfland Swamp. They have asked you to take the gift for them this year.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q0T0_NAME]">Family Reunion</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q0T0_DESC]">Your father has requested your presence in Siria.  You must travel there and meet him.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q0T1_NAME]">Practice Dummy</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q0T1_DESC]">You must learn some basic combat against a Practice Dummy.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q0T2_NAME]">Advanced Combat</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q0T2_DESC]">You must learn some more advanced combat by practicing against a Young Knight.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q1D0_NAME]">Spider Meat</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q1D0_DESC]">Drong the Ogre is looking for someone to hunt down some exotic creatures for him to eat.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q1D1_NAME]">Troll Meat</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q1D1_DESC]">Drong the Ogre is after some more food - this time it is a Troll.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q1D2_NAME]">Wyvern Meat</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q1D2_DESC]">Drong the Ogre is after some more food - this time it is a Wyvern.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q1D3_NAME]">Ogre Meat</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q1D3_DESC]">Drong the Ogre has a special request for you. There is something very unusual that he would like you get for him to eat.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q1D4_NAME]">Serpent Meat</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q1D4_DESC]">Drong the Ogre would like you fetch him a serpent to eat, but not just any serpent will do...</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q1E0_NAME]">Beacon Fires</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q1E0_DESC]">Lord Bane&apos;s servants have been snuffing out the beacon fires in the passes. You must capture new Fire Elementals and re-light them.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q1E1_NAME]">Antidote</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q1E1_DESC]">Neehi the Goblin will pay 150 Gold for each Wasp Stinger you bring him.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q1E2_NAME]">Incoming!</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q1E2_DESC]">The Orc Tribes are building Gobshooters again, and the Dwarves are concerned it may lead to war. You must destroy their latest creation.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q1G1_NAME]">Reagent Hunt</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q1G1_DESC]">Neehi, the Goblin Trader, needs a brave person to go and collect some spell components.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q1G2_NAME]">Tit for Tat</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q1G2_DESC]">Neehi, the Goblin Merchant, needs you to travel over the mountains and exchange some items for him.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q1G3_NAME]">Reassembly</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q1G3_DESC]">Neehi the merchant needs you to take the limb and the axe-head over the mountains to be assembled into an axe.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q1Q0_NAME]">Tribal Chaos</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q1Q0_DESC]">With the death of Dugog, the Orc tribes have been thrown into chaos.  You must travel to 4 Orc villages and defeat their leaders to quiet them down.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q1Q1_NAME]">Lord of Orcs</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q1Q1_DESC]">You must travel deep into Kor to meet with Gruulkar, the Great Orc, Lord of Kor.  You must then convince Gruulkar to tell you why the Orcs are taking prisoners.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q1Q2_NAME]">Ogre Tactics</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q1Q2_DESC]">The Ogres in the south are getting restless.  Somebody needs to travel down there and sort them out.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q1Q3_NAME]">Ogre Magic</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q1Q3_DESC]">You must stop any further threat from the Ogres by defeating their leader.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q1Q4_NAME]">War Council</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q1Q4_DESC]">You must try to stop Gruulkar from gathering the hordes and going to war in Northern Kor.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q1Q5_NAME]">The Gobshooter</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q1Q5_DESC]">Gruulkar is building a new weapon. You must find it and destroy it.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q1Q6_NAME]">Gruulkar</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q1Q6_DESC]">You must travel south and defeat Gruulkar himself.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q1Q7_NAME]">Dragontrap</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q1Q7_DESC]">You must dispose of a Dragon that has been caught in a Dragontrap north of Dhun-Kor.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q1Q8_NAME]">Waking Kelthurax</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q1Q8_DESC]">You must attempt to wake Kelthurax who slumbers beneath the Dragonrealm. He is the oldest Dragon in Etheria.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q1Q9_NAME]">The Mechataur</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q1Q9_DESC]">You must travel to the Hornburg to confront the Mechataur.  Hopefully, you will discover who or what is behind the attacks on your homeland.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q1R0_NAME]">Frost Hunt</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q1R0_DESC]">You must travel to the lair of the Frost Dragon, Chilblain, to see if he is still there.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q1R1_NAME]">Flame Hunt</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q1R1_DESC]">You must search the lair of Umbra the Flame Dragon, to see if there is any sign of where the Dragons have gone.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q1R2_NAME]">Swamp Hunt</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q1R2_DESC]">You must travel to the lair of Morass, the Swamp Dragon, to see if you can find any clues about where the Dragons have gone.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q1R3_NAME]">More Hunting</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q1R3_DESC]">You must continue hunting around the Dragonrealm, searching for anything that might be a clue as to the Dragons&apos; whereabouts.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q1S0_NAME]">Dwarven Heirloom</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q1S0_DESC]">An ancient Dwarven heirloom was stolen from one of the previous caravans attacked by Ogres.  Khalkus would like you to retrieve it.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q1S1_NAME]">The Worm Turns</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q1S1_DESC]">A giant worm has been seen in Eastern Kor. It is said to have swallowed a huge treasure.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q1S2_NAME]">The Sting</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q1S2_DESC]">You must defeat two Giant Scorpions that live in a cave north of Dhun-Kor.  They have been harrassing miners from the city on their way to the mountains.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q1S3_NAME]">Slave Caravan</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q1S3_DESC]">Some Orcs were sighted traveling though Northern Kor with a group of slaves they captured in Agaria. You must stop them.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q1S4_NAME]">Crazy Goblin</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q1S4_DESC]">A crazy Goblin thief has stolen a relic from the Temple of Ymorgia in Gruuldok.  He was seen last near White Skull.  You must find him and retrieve the relic.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q2G0_NAME]">Gnoll in a Hole</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q2G0_DESC]">You have found a Gnoll hiding in a hole in the ground.  You must try and find out what is wrong, and then help him.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q2G1_NAME]">Gnoll Hunters</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q2G1_DESC]">You must find three more Assassins that are after Patch the Gnoll.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q2G2_NAME]">Master Assassin</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q2G2_DESC]">You must tie up one final loose end to help Patch the Gnoll.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q2I0_NAME]">Prized Helm</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q2I0_DESC]">You must travel to Arik&apos;s Arena to battle the Minotaur King and recover a magical Helm.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q2I1_NAME]">Sacred Flame</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q2I1_DESC]">You must journey to the Volcano and help the Firewalkers to relight their Sacred Flame.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q2I2_NAME]">Gnoll Raiders</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q2I2_DESC]">You must chase away the Gnolls that have been desecrating the Pike.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q2I3_NAME]">Endless War</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q2I3_DESC]">Rogue Minotaur tribes are causing havok in the Realms of War. Track them down and stop them.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q2I4_NAME]">Arioc Blockade</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q2I4_DESC]">The pass to Ar has been blocked by Hill Giants.  You must confront them, chase them away and clear a path.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q2I5_NAME]">The Invitations</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q2I5_DESC]">You must deliver an invitation to two Giants, Jarl and Jotun.  They have been invited to attend a tournament in Tusk.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q2I6_NAME]">Fresh Eyes</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q2I6_DESC]">You must somehow replace the Orb you stole from the Elves of Silvermyr.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q2J0_NAME]">Jarl&apos;s Hammer</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q2J0_DESC]">Jotun the Fire Giant has stolen Jarl&apos;s Hammer. You must take it back and return it to its rightful owner.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q2J1_NAME]">Jotun&apos;s Helm</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q2J1_DESC]">Jarl the Frost Giant has stolen Jotun&apos;s Helm. You must find and return it.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q2J2_NAME]">Jarl&apos;s Cloak</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q2J2_DESC]">Jotun the Fire Giant has stolen Jarl&apos;s Cloak. You must take it back and return it to its rightful owner.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q2J3_NAME]">Jotun&apos;s Boots</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q2J3_DESC]">Jarl the Frost Giant has stolen Jotun&apos;s Boots. You must find them and return them.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q2J4_NAME]">Brotherly Love</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q2J4_DESC]">You must try to put an end to Jarl and Jotun stealing each others&apos; things.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q2M0_NAME]">Red-Axe</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q2M0_DESC]">You must seek out the Minotaur, Red-Axe, to train you and improve your skills with the axe.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q2M1_NAME]">Trial of the Wyvern</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q2M1_DESC]">You must travel to the Wyverns&apos; Roost, slaying a Wyvern and studying its combat technique to learn more about using an axe.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q2M2_NAME]">Trial of the Worm</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q2M2_DESC]">You must travel to the Worm Cave, slaying a Sandworm and studying its combat technique to learn more about using an axe.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q2M3_NAME]">Trial of the Scorpion</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q2M3_DESC]">You must travel to the Scorpions&apos; Cave, slay a Giant Scorpion while studying its combat technique to learn more about using an axe.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q2M4_NAME]">Trial of Blood</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q2M4_DESC]">You must complete the final trial in your effort to become a Master of the Axe.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q2Q0_NAME]">Slave Trail</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q2Q0_DESC]">You have followed the trail of the Orcish Slavers to a huge Horned Temple. You must enter the Temple to learn more.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q2Q1_NAME]">Trial by Fire</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q2Q1_DESC]">You must undergo a ritual cleansing by the Minotaur Firewalkers.  Once you have done this, they will agree to talk to you.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q2Q2_NAME]">Horns of Sartek</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q2Q2_DESC]">You must challenge a Minotaur Tribe in an attempt to reclaim the Horns of Sartek.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q2Q3_NAME]">Eye of Sartek</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q2Q3_DESC]">You must obtain the Eye of Sartek from the Elves and return it to the Horned Temple.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q2Q4_NAME]">Tail of Sartek</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q2Q4_DESC]">You must defeat a Minotaur Slaver who wields the legendary Tail of Sartek as a whip.  Then you must return the Tail to the Horned Temple.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q2Q5_NAME]">Tooth of Sartek</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q2Q5_DESC]">You must obtain the Tooth of Sartek from the Gnoll Chieftain in Hyaan and return it to Tauron.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q2Q6_NAME]">Spine of Sartek</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q2Q6_DESC]">You must travel into Southern Kor and find an Ogre Mage that has made the Spine of Sartek into a war banner.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q2Q7_NAME]">Ribs of Sartek</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q2Q7_DESC]">Somewhere in the Realms of War a Minotaur King has hidden the Ribs of Sartek.  You must find them.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q2Q8_NAME]">Crest of Sartek</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q2Q8_DESC]">You must find a Knight in the Borderlands who has had the Crest of Sartek mounted onto his helm, then return to Tauron with the Crest.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q2Q9_NAME]">Skull of Sartek</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q2Q9_DESC]">You must steal the final piece of Sartek, his huge skull, from Minogoth in the Horned Citadel of Ohtar.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q3A0_NAME]">Ice Statues</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q3A0_DESC]">A Medusa has been attacking travelers near Iceguard Keep and turning them into Ice Statues.  You must stop her.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q3A1_NAME]">Children of Ragnar</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q3A1_DESC]">Sensing the unrest in this region, young Dragons - children of Ragnar the Ancient Frost Dragon - have been moving down to the coast. You must chase them away.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q3A2_NAME]">Harpy Queen</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q3A2_DESC]">Harpies from the Hagstone have been traveling down into the High Elven lands. You must confront their Queen to stop them.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q3A3_NAME]">Dark Dealings</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q3A3_DESC]">Dark Dwarven caravans have been sighted leaving for Lord Bane&apos;s Citadel. You must stop them from trading with him.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q3A4_NAME]">Spawn of Bane</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q3A4_DESC]">Arboleth have been sighted near the Lake of Blood. You must drive them away.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q3D0_NAME]">Bloodstone</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q3D0_DESC]">You must search for signs of Elistara&apos;s lost dragon, Crystal, at the Bloodstone.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q3D1_NAME]">Dragontracks</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q3D1_DESC]">You must continue your search through the Realms of Death for Elistara&apos;s lost Dragon.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q3D2_NAME]">Condolences</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q3D2_DESC]">You must accompany Elistara to the Realm of Dragons.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q3D3_NAME]">Sign of Dragons</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q3D3_DESC]">You must hunt down the lost dragons and find out what has happened to them.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q3D4_NAME]">Dragon in Chains</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q3D4_DESC]">You must help Flicker to finally find his mother.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q3E0_NAME]">Gold of Morass</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q3E0_DESC]">You must search Morass&apos; Lair for treasure. You must be cautious. There are Swamp Dragons about!</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q3E1_NAME]">Gold of Umbra</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q3E1_DESC]">You must search Umbra&apos;s Lair for treasure. You must be cautious. There are Flame Dragons about!</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q3E2_NAME]">Gold of Chilblain</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q3E2_DESC]">You must search Chilbain&apos;s Lair for treasure. You must be cautious. There are Frost Dragons about!</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q3I0_NAME]">Royal Summons</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q3I0_DESC]">You have been summoned to appear before Queen Ehlanna at Ehlariel.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q3I1_NAME]">Elven Forge</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q3I1_DESC]">Undead have taken over the Ice Crystal Mine near Iceguard Keep. You must help take back the mine.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q3I2_NAME]">Elven Captives</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q3I2_DESC]">Elven Warriors have been taken captive by the Undead. You must rescue them before it is too late.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q3I3_NAME]">The Baneguard</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q3I3_DESC]">You must travel to Iceguard Keep to pick up the trail left by the Undead in order to rescue the remaining captives.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q3Q0_NAME]">Gornak&apos;s Gap</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q3Q0_DESC]">You must cross the mountains into the Realms of Death in search of Lord Bane.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q3Q1_NAME]">Northern Tundra</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q3Q1_DESC]">You must travel to the Ruins of Ylarie in the Northern Tundra and seek help from the High Elves who guard the remaining two passes into Lord Bane&apos;s realm.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q3Q2_NAME]">Ylarie Defense</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q3Q2_DESC]">You must help the High Elves defend Ylarie against waves of Undead attackers.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q3Q3_NAME]">Skullguard Keep</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q3Q3_DESC]">You must help the High Elves to recapture Skullguard Keep.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q3Q4_NAME]">The Future</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q3Q4_DESC]">You must gather some herbs for the High Elven Mages who need them to cast a spell of farseeing.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q3Q5_NAME]">Three Skulls</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q3Q5_DESC]">You must find and defeat the three Generals of Lord Bane&apos;s army, evil Sorcerors who are preparing his army of Undead.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q3Q6_NAME]">Bane&apos;s Citadel</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q3Q6_DESC]">You must enter Bane&apos;s Citadel and make your way to his throne room, ready to confront him.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q3Q7_NAME]">The Final Battle</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q3Q7_DESC]">You must confront and defeat Lord Bane.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q3S0_NAME]">Follow the Sword</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q3S0_DESC]">You must &apos;follow your sword&apos; in search of a great source of power.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q3W0_NAME]">Wolf Pack</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q3W0_DESC]">A pack of wolves have been terrorizing the Elves at Tirianin. You must chase the wolves away.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q3W1_NAME]">Lost Cubs</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q3W1_DESC]">You must rescue the wolf cubs from being sacrificed by the Doomknight.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q3W2_NAME]">Blessings</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_Q3W2_DESC]">You must bless the homeland of the wolves. To do this, you must first obtain the Elvenstone from Queen Ehlanna.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_QA00_NAME]">Distant Rumor</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_QA00_DESC]">You must help Darkhunter search for an old acquaintance in Northern Kor.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_QA01_NAME]">Seeking Advice</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_QA01_DESC]">Darkhunter wants to travel to Maethelburg and meet with Lord Greythane.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_QA02_NAME]">Liandra&apos;s Offer</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_QA02_DESC]">Darkhunter wants to go and meet an old acquaintance and would like you to come with him.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_QA03_NAME]">Liandra&apos;s Return</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_QA03_DESC]">Darkhunter has received another summons to meet with Liandra. You must accompany him once again.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_QA04_NAME]">Ashes to Ashes</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_QA04_DESC]">You must accompany Darkhunter as he returns Liandra&apos;s ashes to her home in Maethelburg.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_QD00_NAME]">Granite</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_QD00_DESC]">You must find some granite for Drong to eat.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_QD01_NAME]">Volcanic Rock</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_QD01_DESC]">You must travel to the Volcano with Drong and help him find some tasty Volcanic Rock. The Volcano is home to many Fire Elementals.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_QD02_NAME]">Sandstone</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_QD02_DESC]">You must travel to the beach at Tirianin to help find sandstone for Drong to eat. The beach is guarded by Sea Serpents.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_QD03_NAME]">Diamond</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_QD03_DESC]">You must travel to the Lake of Blood to help find diamonds for Drong to eat. The Dark Dwarves are fiercely protective of their diamonds.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_QK00_NAME]">First Gear</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_QK00_DESC]">Khalkus would like you to help him find part of a device called the Great Machine.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_QK01_NAME]">Second Gear</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_QK01_DESC]">You must help Khalkus find the second part of the Great Machine.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_QK02_NAME]">Third Gear</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_QK02_DESC]">You must help Khalkus find the third piece of the Great Machine.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_QK04_NAME]">Fourth Gear</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_QK04_DESC]">You must help Khalkus gather the fourth piece of the Great Machine.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_QK05_NAME]">Fifth Gear</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_QK05_DESC]">You must help Khalkus find the fifth piece of the Great Machine.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_QK06_NAME]">Assembly Required</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_QK06_DESC]">You must finally help Khalkus put the Great Machine together.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_QP00_NAME]">Patch&apos;s Hoard</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_QP00_DESC]">Patch invites you to Hyaan to see his treasure.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_QP01_NAME]">Ill-Gotten Gains</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_QP01_DESC]">Track down the thief who stole Patch&apos;s treasure.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_QP02_NAME]">The Vault</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_QP02_DESC]">You must travel to Dhun-Kor with Khalkus and Patch to help build a vault for Patch&apos;s treasure.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_QS00_NAME]">Secret Message</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_QS00_DESC]">Princess Serephine receives a secret message from a friend at Enmouth asking for help. You must travel to Enmouth to help Serephine&apos;s friend.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_QS01_NAME]">Shotgun Wedding</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_QS01_DESC]">You must travel to The Trarg and rescue Princess Serephine.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_QS02_NAME]">Imperial Legion</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_QS02_DESC]">Emperor Selentius has sent a legion of Imperial Guards to search for Princess Serephine and take her home to Enmouth. Tread cautiously.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_QU00_NAME]">Age of Honor</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_QU00_DESC]">Sunspear wishes to talk with you about battling a Frost Giant.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_QU01_NAME]">Seeking Death</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_QU01_DESC]">Sunspear wishes to observe you fighting an Arboleth.</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_QU02_NAME]">A Worthy Foe</Text>
   <Text tag="[QUEST_QU02_DESC]">Help Sunspear choose the final foe that he wishes to face.</Text>

</TextLibrary>
