<?xml version="1.0"?>
<TextLibrary>

   <Text tag="[CITY_CBAR_NAME]">Bartonia</Text>
   <Text tag="[CITY_CBAR_DESC]">The largest city belonging to the Knights of Agaria.</Text>
   <Text tag="[CITY_CDKO_NAME]">Dhun-Kor</Text>
   <Text tag="[CITY_CDKO_DESC]">This Dwarven Outpost does much trade with the Orcs, Goblins and Ogres of Kor.</Text>
   <Text tag="[CITY_CDRA_NAME]">Drakenburg</Text>
   <Text tag="[CITY_CDRA_DESC]">This citadel is built at the foot of the Drakenburg mountain - home to a huge Green Dragon.</Text>
   <Text tag="[CITY_CDRH_NAME]">Dragonrealm</Text>
   <Text tag="[CITY_CDRH_DESC]">Few mortals have entered the Dragonrealm and returned to tell the tale.</Text>
   <Text tag="[CITY_CEHL_NAME]">Ehlariel</Text>
   <Text tag="[CITY_CEHL_DESC]">The Citadel of Ehlariel is home to the Ice Queen, Ehlanna, one of the two rulers of the High Elves.</Text>
   <Text tag="[CITY_CENM_NAME]">Enmouth</Text>
   <Text tag="[CITY_CENM_DESC]">Enmouth is the largest trade port in the Selentine Empire.</Text>
   <Text tag="[CITY_CGAL_NAME]">Gallia</Text>
   <Text tag="[CITY_CGAL_DESC]">The golden-walled city of Gallia is the oldest citadel in the Borderlands.</Text>
   <Text tag="[CITY_CGLK_NAME]">Gluk</Text>
   <Text tag="[CITY_CGLK_DESC]">Gluk is a city full of Ogres in Southern Kor, ruled by a cruel and powerful Ogre Mage.</Text>
   <Text tag="[CITY_CGRU_NAME]">Gruuldok</Text>
   <Text tag="[CITY_CGRU_DESC]">Gruuldok is the birthplace of the Great Orc, Gruulkar, current leader of the Orcs of Kor.</Text>
   <Text tag="[CITY_CHTP_NAME]">Horned Temple</Text>
   <Text tag="[CITY_CHTP_DESC]">The Minotaur Firewalkers within these walls await the return of their God, Sartek.</Text>
   <Text tag="[CITY_CHYA_NAME]">Hyaan</Text>
   <Text tag="[CITY_CHYA_DESC]">Hyaan is home to the Hyaa clan of Gnolls, a fierce and dangerous group of creatures.</Text>
   <Text tag="[CITY_CJAK_NAME]">Jarl&apos;s Keep</Text>
   <Text tag="[CITY_CJAK_DESC]">Jarl, Lord of the Frost Giants, lives in this massive citadel.</Text>
   <Text tag="[CITY_CJOK_NAME]">Jotun&apos;s Keep</Text>
   <Text tag="[CITY_CJOK_DESC]">Jotun, Lord of the Fire Giants, lives in this huge citadel.</Text>
   <Text tag="[CITY_CKUN_NAME]">Kal-Ungar</Text>
   <Text tag="[CITY_CKUN_DESC]">The evil machinery of the Dark Dwarves can be heard from this citadel churning all day and all night.</Text>
   <Text tag="[CITY_CLBC_NAME]">Bane&apos;s Citadel</Text>
   <Text tag="[CITY_CLBC_DESC]">This citadel is home to Lord Bane, Master of the Undead, also known as the Dark Horseman of Death.</Text>
   <Text tag="[CITY_COHT_NAME]">Ohtar</Text>
   <Text tag="[CITY_COHT_DESC]">Ohtar was the home of Sartek, Lord of War and King of the Minotaurs, before he was defeated by Lord Bane.</Text>
   <Text tag="[CITY_CSIL_NAME]">Silvermyr</Text>
   <Text tag="[CITY_CSIL_DESC]">Silvermyr is the only forest on the mainland of Etheria where the Wood Elves may still be found.</Text>
   <Text tag="[CITY_CTRA_NAME]">The Trarg</Text>
   <Text tag="[CITY_CTRA_DESC]">Nomadic tribes of barbarians roam these plains with their herds of horses.</Text>
   <Text tag="[CITY_CTSK_NAME]">Tusk</Text>
   <Text tag="[CITY_CTSK_DESC]">A central gathering place for many tribes of Minotaurs, Tusk was once home to the arena where Sartek staged the battles of the K&apos;Varr.</Text>
   <Text tag="[CITY_CYLA_NAME]">Ylarie</Text>
   <Text tag="[CITY_CYLA_DESC]">Partially left in ruins by Orc invasions many centuries ago, Ylarie was once a beautiful Elven city.</Text>

   <Text tag="[RUIN_RATO_NAME]">Arik&apos;s Arena</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUIN_RATO_DESC]">This is the home of Arik, the minotaur king.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUIN_RBST_NAME]">Bloodstone</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUIN_RBST_DESC]">This rock formation marks the place where Lord Bane was once defeated by the Elven Mages.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUIN_RCBL_NAME]">Chilblain&apos;s Lair</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUIN_RCBL_DESC]">The Frost Dragon, Chilblain, lives here.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUIN_RDCV_NAME]">Dragon Cave</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUIN_RDCV_DESC]">This cave belongs to a Green Dragon who has lived within sight of Drakenburg for many centuries.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUIN_RDGV_NAME]">Dragons&apos; Graveyard</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUIN_RDGV_DESC]">The bones of Dragons litter the ground in this silent valley.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUIN_RDPS_NAME]">Dark Path Shrine</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUIN_RDPS_DESC]">Members of the Dark Path Cult are said to worship at this shrine.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUIN_RDSH_NAME]">Dragon Shrine</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUIN_RDSH_DESC]">This is an ancient Elven shrine, originally used to worship the Frost Dragons who lived in these mountains.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUIN_RDST_NAME]">Dark Stables</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUIN_RDST_DESC]">Lord Bane keeps his mounts stabled in these dark uninviting caves.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUIN_REGB_NAME]">Egor&apos;s Bridge</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUIN_REGB_DESC]">Egor the Troll lives under this Bridge.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUIN_RGSE_NAME]">Gildine Sewers</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUIN_RGSE_DESC]">These sewers carry away the wastes from the busy citadel of Gildor.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUIN_RHAG_NAME]">Hagstone</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUIN_RHAG_DESC]">The Hagstone is home to a large coven of Harpies.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUIN_RICM_NAME]">Ice Crystal Mine</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUIN_RICM_DESC]">The Elves have dug deep into the Ice here, mining precious metals.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUIN_RMOL_NAME]">Morass&apos; Lair</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUIN_RMOL_DESC]">The Swamp Dragon, Morass, lives here.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUIN_ROOU_NAME]">Old Outpost</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUIN_ROOU_DESC]">This was once a Selentine military outpost, but Elenian archers destroyed it.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUIN_ROTO_NAME]">Ogre&apos;s Tower</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUIN_ROTO_DESC]">Two Ogres live in this tower on the edge of the Barad Dumyr.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUIN_RSCC_NAME]">Scorpions&apos; Cave</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUIN_RSCC_DESC]">Giant Scorpions inhabit this cave and terrorize any passersby.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUIN_RSCV_NAME]">Swamp Cave</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUIN_RSCV_DESC]">An ancient Flame Dragon is said to slumber in this cave.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUIN_RSKM_NAME]">Skell Marshes</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUIN_RSKM_DESC]">These marshes are home to all manner of foul and twisted creatures.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUIN_RSLV_NAME]">Slaver Camp</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUIN_RSLV_DESC]">Minotaur Slavers often land here and raid southern Selentia and the Trarg.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUIN_RSTR_NAME]">Ancient Grove</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUIN_RSTR_DESC]">An ancient order of Elenian Druids worship at this Grove.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUIN_RTHC_NAME]">Royal Crypt</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUIN_RTHC_DESC]">The Kings of Theira are buried here.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUIN_RTLH_NAME]">Troll Hole</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUIN_RTLH_DESC]">Trolls live in this cave deep within the marsh.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUIN_RUML_NAME]">Umbra&apos;s Lair</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUIN_RUML_DESC]">The Flame Dragon, Umbra, lives here.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUIN_RVOL_NAME]">Volcano</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUIN_RVOL_DESC]">This Volcano is home to a large number of Fire Elementals.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUIN_RWCV_NAME]">Worm Cave</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUIN_RWCV_DESC]">Giant worms live here. The Orcs of Kor highly prize them for their meat.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUIN_RWGS_NAME]">Wargstone</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUIN_RWGS_DESC]">Out west of Gruuldok, the plains are infested by Wargs.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUIN_RWHV_NAME]">Wasp Hive</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUIN_RWHV_DESC]">Giant Wasps inhabit a hive within this cave.</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUIN_RWRO_NAME]">Wyvern&apos;s Roost</Text>
   <Text tag="[RUIN_RWRO_DESC]">A pack of Wyverns live on a peak at the end of a long, dry valley.</Text>

   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WELE_NAME]">Elenia</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WELE_DESC]">The Elenian Knights guard the western forests of Agaria from Selentine invasions.</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WGIL_NAME]">Gildor</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WGIL_DESC]">The Gildine Knights are the wealthiest and most powerful order of the Agarian Knights.</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WSIR_NAME]">Siria</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WSIR_DESC]">The Sirian Knights are famed for their mighty Paladins.</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WTHR_NAME]">Theira</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WTHR_DESC]">The Theiran Knights protect the northern borders of Agaria from hordes of ravenous Trolls.</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WRAR_NAME]">Ruins of Artum</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WRAR_DESC]">This gateway once guarded the path through the Sserin Jungle.</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WMAE_NAME]">Maethelburg</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WMAE_DESC]">Maethelburg is home to the Riverguard - an order of Warriors who protect the Borderlands.</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WAPS_NAME]">Agarian Pass</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WAPS_DESC]">Dwarves guard this pass over the Mountains of Agaria.</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WSKE_NAME]">Skellheim</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WSKE_DESC]">The Duke of Skellheim is rumored to be a master of the Dark Arts.</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WBTH_NAME]">Barthel</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WBTH_DESC]">This village is a trade center for Southern Selentia.</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WHPS_NAME]">Hammer Pass</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WHPS_DESC]">This Pass is usually well-guarded, since any invading Orc Tribes invariably seek to enter Agaria through here.</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WALF_NAME]">Alfland</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WALF_DESC]">The men of Alfland trade freely with the Wood Elves of Silvermyr.</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WRMO_NAME]">Blood Moon</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WRMO_DESC]">The Blood Moon Orcs can see keenly in the dark. They launch their raids at night.</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WWSK_NAME]">White Skull</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WWSK_DESC]">It is said that the Shaman of the White Skull Orcs can raise the dead.</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WBHE_NAME]">Bone Head</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WBHE_DESC]">The Bone Head Orcs pierce their ears and noses in dozens of places, filling them with animal bones.</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WSFA_NAME]">Snake Fang</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WSFA_DESC]">The Snake Fang Orcs are rumored to have a poisonous bite.</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WGRK_NAME]">Gork</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WGRK_DESC]">Gork is home to a band of vicious Ogres.</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WDRT_NAME]">Drong&apos;s Tower</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WDRT_DESC]">Drong the Ogre lives in this tower.  Drong&apos;s feasts are legendary - he is a magnificent cook.</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WNKR_NAME]">Northern Kor</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WNKR_DESC]">Northern Kor is a relative wasteland.  Too many wars between the Orcs and the dragons have scarred the ground.</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WDPS_NAME]">Dragon Valley</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WDPS_DESC]">This long valley is the entrance to the Dragonrealm.</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WVOK_NAME]">Valley of Kings</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WVOK_DESC]">There is rumored to be an Ancient Dwarven Tomb somewhere in this valley.</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WHBG_NAME]">Hornburg</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WHBG_DESC]">The Dwarves named this peak Hornburg, since it marked the entrance to the homelands of the Minotaurs.</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WPIK_NAME]">The Pike</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WPIK_DESC]">This pike is ritually decorated with the heads of those foolish enough to trespass in the Realms of War.</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WGWK_NAME]">Giants&apos; Walk</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WGWK_DESC]">Giants are frequently seen traveling through these lands.</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WSHD_NAME]">Blackhoof</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WSHD_DESC]">The fierce Blackhoof tribe rule this village.</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WWRT_NAME]">Weret</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WWRT_DESC]">This village of shapechangers is feared by the many tribes of Minotaurs to the south.</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WPAR_NAME]">Ar</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WPAR_DESC]">The chilly Plains of Ar are home to many barbaric tribes.</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WGGP_NAME]">Gornak&apos;s Gap</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WGGP_DESC]">Garnak&apos;s Gap is one of the few passes into the Realms of Death. It is inhabited by bands of ravenous Undead Orcs.</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WSGK_NAME]">Skullguard Keep</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WSGK_DESC]">Skullguard Keep guards the High Elven lands from the Undead in the north.</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WIGK_NAME]">Iceguard Keep</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WIGK_DESC]">Iceguard Keep is one of the two Keeps the High Elves use to defend their lands from Lord Bane.</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WRAG_NAME]">Ragnar&apos;s Coast</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WRAG_DESC]">Ragnar, the ancient Frost Dragon, lives in the mountains nearby and claims this coast as his own.</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WETO_NAME]">Eldros&apos; Tower</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WETO_DESC]">This tower was the home of the ancient Elven Healer, Lord Eldros.</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WGRW_NAME]">Graww</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WGRW_DESC]">Graww was the birthplace of Gornak Elfeater, one of the mightiest Orcs to ever invade the civilized lands.</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WSOI_NAME]">Sea of Ice</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WSOI_DESC]">Beyond the northern borders of the Realms of Death lies an endless sea of jagged shards of ice.</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WLOB_NAME]">Lake of Blood</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WLOB_DESC]">It is often said that Lord Bane draws some of his power from the red waters of this lake.</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WTIR_NAME]">Tirianin</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WTIR_DESC]">Tirianin is the busiest port of the High Elves on the mainland.</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WSMZ_NAME]">Sartek&apos;s Maze</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WSMZ_DESC]">Many twisted and misshapen creatures inhabit these twisting valleys.</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WBBR_NAME]">Bonebridge</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WBBR_DESC]">Doomknights guard this bridge that leads towards Lord Bane&apos;s citadel.</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WWAS_NAME]">The Wastelands</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WWAS_DESC]">There is very little to see upon these cold windy plains.</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WHVA_NAME]">Hidden Valley</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WHVA_DESC]">An ancient secret road of the Dark Dwarves leads up this valley.</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WBSP_NAME]">Bloodspring</Text>
   <Text tag="[WAYPOINT_WBSP_DESC]">This secret spring is the source of the Lake of Blood.</Text>

</TextLibrary>
